<Publish>
	<ModId Value="137029" />
	<DisplayName Value="CityForge" />
	<ShortDescription Value="All-in-one cheat panel. Money, milestones, demand, construction, citizens, buildings, storage and more — no restarts needed." />
	<LongDescription><![CDATA[

# **CityForge — All-in-One Cheat Panel**

CityForge puts a button in your toolbar. Click it and a floating panel opens with every cheat you could want, organized into clear sections.

Everything saves automatically and comes back exactly as you left it next session.

Built for sandbox players, creative builders, and anyone who would rather focus on building than fighting the economy.

---

# **Money**

Add or remove money instantly in fixed amounts:

100K
1M
10M
50M

Or simply enable **Infinite Money** and never think about it again.

---

# **Milestones & Development Tree**

Advance to any specific milestone **(1–20)** or unlock all of them at once.

Keep them permanently unlocked so the game cannot take them back.

One button also grants **228 development tree points**.

---

# **Demand**

Override residential demand separately for:

Low Density
Medium Density
High Density

Commercial, Industrial and Office demand each have their own sliders.

Each zone also includes a **Force Build** toggle that ignores demand entirely and forces buildings to grow — perfect when the AI refuses to cooperate.

---

# **Construction Time**

**Instant Construction** completes everything the moment you place it.

If that is too extreme, choose one of four speed levels:

½×
1×
2×
4×

Switch between them anytime without restarting the game.

---

# **Citizens & Tourism**

Boost move-in speed with a multiplier up to **10×** so your zones actually fill up.

Apply the same boost to tourists.

Additional options include:

- **Max Happiness** — keeps every citizen permanently happy
- **Rich Citizens** — gives every household 500,000 money every few in-game minutes
- **Max Education** — instantly sets all citizens to the highest education level (Level 4)
- **Education Distribution** — set custom percentages for each education level across all citizens

---

# **Buildings & Storage**

Upgrade **every building in your city to level 5** with a single click.

The upgrade process runs in small batches in the background so the game stays smooth.

You can also:

- Fill all storage instantly
- Keep storage permanently full
- Set all companies to **100% efficiency**

---

# **Appearance**

Customize the **panel background color** using presets or a custom hex value.

The panel is freely **draggable** and **resizable** — drag the title bar to move it, pull the bottom-right corner to resize.

---

# **General**

Optional setting to **show or hide the toolbar button** — toggle it in the mod settings.

Optional setting to **reset all cheats when loading a new city**, so you always start fresh.

**Keep achievements enabled** even when mods are active — toggle it in the mod settings.

Everything else persists exactly as you left it.

---

Fully translated into:

English, German, French, Spanish, Italian, Portuguese, Polish, Russian, Japanese, Korean, Chinese (Simplified), Chinese (Traditional)

Bug reports and feedback are always welcome.

---

# **CityForge — Alles-in-einem Cheat-Panel**

CityForge fügt einen Button in die Toolbar ein. Ein Klick öffnet ein schwebendes Panel mit allen Cheats — übersichtlich in Bereiche aufgeteilt.

Alle Einstellungen werden automatisch gespeichert und beim nächsten Start genau so wiederhergestellt.

Für Sandbox-Spieler, entspannte Stadtbauer und alle, die lieber bauen als gegen die Wirtschaft anzukämpfen.

---

# **Geld**

Beliebige Beträge sofort einzahlen oder abziehen:

100K
1M
10M
50M

Oder einfach **Unendlich Geld** aktivieren.

---

# **Meilensteine & Entwicklungsbaum**

Bis zu einem bestimmten **Meilenstein (1–20)** vorspulen oder alle gleichzeitig freischalten.

Mit **dauerhaft entsperrt halten** kann das Spiel sie nicht mehr wegnehmen.

Zusätzlich erhältst du **228 Entwicklungsbaum-Punkte**.

---

# **Nachfrage**

Wohnnachfrage getrennt überschreiben für:

Niedrige Dichte
Mittlere Dichte
Hohe Dichte

Gewerbe, Industrie und Büros haben jeweils eigene Regler.

Zusätzlich besitzt jede Zone eine **„Sofort bauen"-Option**, die Gebäude unabhängig von der Nachfrage entstehen lässt.

---

# **Bauzeit**

**Sofortbau** lässt alles direkt nach dem Platzieren fertig werden.

Alternativ stehen vier Geschwindigkeitsstufen zur Verfügung:

½×
1×
2×
4×

Jederzeit umschaltbar — ohne Neustart.

---

# **Bürger & Tourismus**

Die Einzugsrate kann mit bis zu **10×** erhöht werden, damit Gebäude schneller voll werden.

Dasselbe gilt für Touristen.

Weitere Optionen:

- **Maximale Zufriedenheit** – alle Bürger bleiben dauerhaft glücklich
- **Reiche Bürger** – jeder Haushalt erhält alle paar Spielminuten 500.000 Geld
- **Maximale Bildung** – setzt alle Bürger sofort auf das höchste Bildungsniveau (Stufe 4)
- **Bildungsverteilung** – legt fest, wie viel Prozent der Bürger welches Bildungsniveau haben

---

# **Gebäude & Lager**

Alle Gebäude der Stadt mit **einem Klick auf Stufe 5 upgraden**.

Die Verarbeitung erfolgt in kleinen Batches im Hintergrund, damit das Spiel flüssig bleibt.

Zusätzlich kannst du:

- Alle Lager sofort auffüllen
- Lager dauerhaft voll halten
- Alle Unternehmen auf **100 % Effizienz** setzen

---

# **Erscheinungsbild**

Die **Hintergrundfarbe des Panels** lässt sich mit Voreinstellungen oder einem eigenen Hex-Wert anpassen.

Das Panel ist frei **verschiebbar** und **in der Größe veränderbar** — Titelleiste zum Verschieben ziehen, untere rechte Ecke zum Skalieren.

---

# **Allgemein**

Optional kann der **Toolbar-Button ein- oder ausgeblendet** werden — umschaltbar in den Mod-Einstellungen.

Optional können **alle Cheats beim Laden einer neuen Karte zurückgesetzt** werden.

**Erfolge aktiv halten** — auch wenn Mods aktiv sind. Umschaltbar in den Mod-Einstellungen.

Alles andere bleibt genau so gespeichert, wie du es verlassen hast.

Vollständig übersetzt in:

Englisch, Deutsch, Französisch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Portugiesisch, Polnisch, Russisch, Japanisch, Koreanisch, Chinesisch (Vereinfacht), Chinesisch (Traditionell)

Bugreports und Feedback sind jederzeit willkommen.
]]></LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Assets/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/Screenshot1.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/Screenshot2.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/Screenshot3.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/Screenshot4.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/Screenshot5.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Assets/Screenshot6.png" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/cheatbox-cheat-panel-for-money-demand-construction-more.1906532/" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.13" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.*.*" />
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<ChangeLog Value="v1.0.13&#10;&#10;IMPROVEMENTS&#10;&#10;• All panel sections are now collapsible, click any section header to fold or expand it&#10;&#10;BUG FIXES&#10;&#10;• Fixed ArgumentException on launch caused by a duplicate key in the Chinese (Simplified) locale" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/venatorax/CityForge" />
	<ExternalLink Type="donation" Url="https://paypal.me/venatoraxx" />
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
